freeadvertisingforyou.com 2018-12-29

# FreeAdvertisingForYou! Free Traffic Exchange | Free Advertising Free Web Traffic

Welcome to FreeAdvertisingForYou (the "Site"). 

We understand that privacy online is important to users of our Site, especially when conducting business. This statement governs our privacy policies with respect to those users of the Site ("Visitors") who visit without transacting business and Visitors who register to transact business on the Site and make use of the various services offered by FreeAdvertisingForYou (collectively, "Services") ("Authorized Customers"). 

**Definitions:** "Personally Identifiable Information" refers to any information that identifies or can be used to identify, contact, or locate the person to whom such information pertains, including, but not limited to, name, address, phone number, fax number, email address, financial profiles, social security number, and credit card information. Personally Identifiable Information does not include information that is collected anonymously (that is, without identification of the individual user) or demographic information not connected to an identified individual. 

**What Personally Identifiable Information is collected?** We may collect basic user profile information from all of our Visitors. We collect the following additional information from our Authorized Customers: the names, addresses, phone numbers and email addresses of Authorized Customers, the nature and size of the business, and the nature and size of the advertising inventory that the Authorized Customer intends to purchase or sell. 

**How does the Site use Personally Identifiable Information?** We use Personally Identifiable Information to customize the Site, to make appropriate service offerings, and to fulfill buying and selling requests on the Site. We may email Visitors and Authorized Customers about research or purchase and selling opportunities on the Site or information related to the subject matter of the Site. We may also use Personally Identifiable Information to contact Visitors and Authorized Customers in response to specific inquiries, or to provide requested information. 

**How is Personally Identifiable Information stored?** Personally Identifiable Information collected by FreeAdvertisingForYou is securely stored and is not accessible to third parties. 

**Analytics.** We use Google Analytics to measure and evaluate access to and traffic on the Public Area of the Site, and create user navigation reports for our Site administrators. Google operates independently from us and has its own privacy policy, which we strongly suggest you review. Google may use the information collected through Google Analytics to evaluate Users' and Visitors' activity on our Site.  
For more information, see [Google Analytics Privacy and Data Sharing.](https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245)

We take measures to protect the technical information collected by our use of Google Analytics. The data collected will only be used on a need to know basis to resolve technical issues, administer the Site and identify visitor preferences; but in this case, the data will be in non-identifiable form. We do not use any of this information to identify Visitors or Users.

**What choices are available to Visitors regarding collection, use and distribution of the information?** Visitors and Authorized Customers may opt out of receiving unsolicited information from or being contacted by us and/or our vendors and affiliated agencies by responding to emails as instructed, or by contacting us at jason@freeadvertisingforyou.com 

**Are Cookies Used on the Site?** Cookies are used for a variety of reasons. We use Cookies to obtain information about the preferences of our Visitors and the services they select. We also use Cookies for security purposes to protect our Authorized Customers. 

**How does FreeAdvertisingForYou use login information?** FreeAdvertisingForYou uses login information, including, but not limited to, IP addresses, ISPs, and browser types, to analyze trends, administer the Site, track a user's movement and use, and gather broad demographic information. 

**How can Visitors correct any inaccuracies in Personally Identifiable Information?** Visitors and Authorized Customers may contact us to update Personally Identifiable Information about them or to correct any inaccuracies by emailing us at jason@freeadvertisingforyou.com 

**Can a Visitor delete or deactivate Personally Identifiable Information collected by the Site?** We provide Visitors and Authorized Customers with a mechanism to delete/deactivate Personally Identifiable Information from the Site's database by contacting jason@freeadvertisingforyou.com. However, because of backups and records of deletions, it may be impossible to delete a Visitor's entry without retaining some residual information. An individual who requests to have Personally Identifiable Information deactivated will have this information functionally deleted, and we will not sell, transfer, or use Personally Identifiable Information relating to that individual in any way moving forward. Backups are done every day and the last 7 backups are retained. Additionally, a backup from the 1st and 15th are retained. The longest a backup would be retained would be 30 days then, 31 for some months. 

**What happens if the Privacy Policy Changes?** We will let our Visitors and Authorized Customers know about changes to our privacy policy by posting such changes on the Site. However, if we are changing our privacy policy in a manner that might cause disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information that a Visitor or Authorized Customer has previously requested not be disclosed, we will contact such Visitor or Authorized Customer to allow such Visitor or Authorized Customer to prevent such disclosure. 

**Links:** This web site contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
